# PEDRO EDDIE R. REYES, CIE

I am an Oracle ERP consultant with 3 years of experience in Oracle Technology. I also do web developing on my spare time to expand my skills.

Phone: +63 936 046 4957 Portfolio: eddreyes.vercel.app

Email: pedroeddie.reyes@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/pedro-eddie-reyes

## **Experience:**

### PricewaterhouseCoopers International Limited (PwC) – Oracle Technical Associate

March 2023 – Jul 2024

- Created essential BIP reports for the use of a Digital Banking company.
- Created Technical Design Documents for better documentation of integrations.
- Support in connecting Oracle REST API's to third-party applications.
- Lead Technical Design walkthroughs to clients and third-party members of the project.
- Assisted in creating Oracle integrations and implementation.
- Validate if Technical Designs are match with the Functional Design documents to ensure smooth creation of Technical Integrations.

### Accenture Inc. - Associate Software Engineer

May 2021- March 2022

- Integrated clients' APIs through Oracle Cloud Integrations.
- Helped launch websites designed to help customers apply for the client's web services.
- Assisted in writing Technical Documents for clients' websites.

## Citizen Finedevice Philippines Inc. – Production Engineer

March 2019 - September 2020

- Developed standards and work instructions based on calculated analysis.
- Formulate cost-saving methods through indirect material reduction and manpower scheduling.
- Saved costs by reducing unnecessary purchases and efficient order scheduling.

### Skills and Tools Used:

- Oracle BIP Reports
- Oracle Cloud Integrations
- Oracle ERP Fusion
- Oracle SQL
- HTML

- CSS
- Javascript
- React.js
- Bootstrap
- Sass

#### **Education**

## **Bachelor of Science in Industrial Engineering**

De La Salle Lipa - 2012 - 2017

#### Certificate:

- Certified Industrial Engineer (CIE)
- 1Z0-1085-21: Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Foundations 2021 Associate